(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
だから
And so...
君のこと 大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, I love you, I love you...
大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, I love you, I love you!
溢れ出るこの愛はきっともう止まらない
This overflowing love surely won't stop anymore
AI AI AI AI I LOVE YOU 君に...
AI AI AI AI I LOVE YOU to you...
あいあいあいあいらぶゆー
Ai ai ai ai love you
I need you
もっと もっと
More and more,
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want.
夢見るハートがぴょんぴょん
My dreaming heart goes hop hop!
穴に落ちてあみゃあみゃ
I've fallen into a hole, amya amya...
こんなになってもいまだ
Even though it's come to this,
抜け出せない
I still can't find my way out.
どうしたもんかな ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui nui nui...
助けて君たち あほいほい
Save me, everyone! Ahoi-hoi!
もっと もっと もっと
More and more and more,
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want!
どアニメ宣言！
Do Anime Sengen!
アニメにハマって 歌いたくなっちゃった
I'm hooked on anime and felt like singing!
推しのシーン見ながら カラオケ歌えるなんて…
Being able to sing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてツライっ！
It's so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・アニソン見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND
FuRyu
吉野家でごはんしよ
Let's eat at Yoshinoya!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Please enjoy the original's true passion.
牛丼は吉野家
Beef bowls mean Yoshinoya.
やっぱこれだね
It's definitely this.
よくばりうさぎは 止まらない
The greedy rabbit won't stop
ピョンピョン跳ねて どこまでも
Hopping along everywhere
甘いお菓子も 宝物
Sweet treats are treasures too
全部全部 私のもの
Everything, everything is mine
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Attention: To our guests
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
本日は
Today,
ホロライブ 3rd...
Hololive 3rd...
hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun - The Ultimate Idols, You Have to Stan Them!
DAY2にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for joining us for DAY 2!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、
To ensure everyone enjoys the live show until the end,
いくつかご案内させていただきます。
we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、
The use of photography, recording,
録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
and filming equipment is strictly prohibited during the performance.
館内は禁煙となっております。
The entire venue is non-smoking.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、
In the event that you feel unwell, do not overdo it
近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
and please inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、
Moshing, diving, and throwing objects onto the stage
ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり
are strictly prohibited, as they disturb others
公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
or hinder the performance.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
また、本公演は映像配信及び
Also, cameras for streaming and photography
写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
are present in the venue,
客席が映り込む場合があります。
and audience seats may be filmed.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに
These images and videos may be used
使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
for promotional purposes, so please be aware.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは #きゅるるん大作戦DAY2 です。
Also, the hashtag for the live event is #KyururunDaisakusenDAY2.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げて下さい！
Please use the hashtag and spread the excitement!
それでは、開演まであと少しです。
Well then, there's only a little while until the show begins.
君たちの声をいっぱい聴かせてください！
Let us hear your voices!
そして、今からちょっと3期生で円陣を組もうと思っているんですが...
And now, the 3rd generation members are going to form a huddle...
マイクを通さずやりますので、ちょっと静かにして、
We'll be doing it without microphones, so please be quiet
耳を澄ませていただければと思います。
and listen closely.
行くんで、ちょっとしんと待ってください。
We're starting now, so please wait quietly.
行きます！
Here we go!
ぺこ！
Peko!
ふれ！
Flare!
のえ！
Noel!
まり！
Marine!
3期生！
3rd Gen!
おー！
Yeah!
こんぺこ！ 兎田ぺこらぺこ！
Kon-peko! Usada Pekora-peko!
不知火フレアだよ！
I'm Shiranui Flare!
こんまっする！ 白銀ノエルです！
Kon-massuru! I'm Shirogane Noel!
Ahoy! 宝鐘マリンです！
Ahoy! I'm Houshou Marine!
超アイドル 伝説のガールは 欲張り
Super idols, the legendary girls are greedy
笑い合って もっと可愛くなる
Laughing together, we become even cuter
Oh yeah yeah
遠いようでお近付き
Feeling distant yet getting closer
他人なのに家族みたいで
We're like a family even though we're strangers
寝る間も忘れて きゅるるん大作戦
Forgetting even to sleep, it's Operation Kyurulun
喜怒哀楽を分かち合ってさ
Sharing all our joys and sorrows
大きくなっていきたいよね
We want to keep growing bigger
でも小さなことも大事にして
But we'll cherish the little things too
一歩ずつ よし一歩ずつだね
One step at a time, yeah, step by step
楽しんでくれるのが嬉しい
It makes us happy when you're having fun
最高のエンターテイナー
We're the ultimate entertainers
後ろまで見えてる？
Can you see us all the way in the back?
画面の向こうも届いてる
We're reaching you through the screen too
光の海を泳ぐの
Swimming through this sea of light
超アイドル 伝説のガールは 欲張り
Super idols, the legendary girls are greedy
愛されたいし 夢だって見たい
We want to be loved and have dreams,
君じゃなきゃやだ
It has to be you
絶好調です！ 狙い撃ちで
We're in top form! Taking aim...
君にウィンク
And blowing a wink at you!
やっぱ伝説のガールで めっちゃハッピー
After all, being legendary girls makes us so happy
お願いしたいし 応えたいし 叶っちゃう
We have requests, we want to deliver, and dreams come true
先頭走る 勿論君と
Running at the front, of course with you
笑い合って もっと可愛くなる
Laughing together, we become even cuter
Oh yeah yeah
せっかくだからやり切りたいし
Since we're here, we want to give it our all
乗り越える壁はとてもデカい
The walls we have to overcome are huge
将来有望エンターテイナー
Promising entertainers of the future
君が思ってるよりずっと
Much more than you might think...
君のことを想ってる
We're thinking of you
どうかな？ 焦がれた
How is it? The dream we yearned for...
夢には近づけてるかな？
Are we getting any closer to it?
声の限り 頑張れるんだ 聞かせて
We can do our best as long as we have voices, let us hear you!
1, 2, 3, 4!
One, two, three, four!
もう最高！ 伝説のガールは 幸せ
Simply the best! The legendary girls are happy
愛されていける のびしろあって
We can keep being loved, with room for growth,
下向くとやだ
looking down is a no-no
テンポアップし 続けていく
Keeping the tempo up and moving forward
見たい景色へ
Toward the scenery we want to see
世界に出して！ L-O-V-E
Show it to the world! L-O-V-E
限界呼び覚ませ！ L-O-V-E
Wake up the limits! L-O-V-E
今すぐ達せ！ L-O-V-E
Reach it right now! L-O-V-E
皆で作っていく
We're building this all together
イェーイ！
Yay!
後半戦も 盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's keep the excitement going for the second half!
君たち！ まだまだ声出せますよねー！
Everyone! You can still shout louder, right?!
揺らいでも頑張っちゃ
Even if I falter, I'll do my best
褒められて伸びるわ分かってるよね
I grow with praise, you know that, right?
この場所が宝物
This place is a treasure
泣いちゃわないよう笑おう
Let's laugh so we don't cry
君と一緒に！
Together with you!
超アイドル 3rdガールは欲張り
Super idols, 3rd Girls are greedy
愛されたいし夢も見てみたい 君じゃなきゃ
Want to be loved and dream too, it has to be you
ヤダって 絶好調で願い撃ちで君にウインク
Or I'll say no! In top form, I'll shoot a wish and wink
やっぱ3rdガールでめっちゃハッピー
As expected, being a 3rd Girl makes me so happy
あれもしたいしこれもしたいし叶っちゃう
I want to do this and that, and it'll all come true
全力で走る もちろん君と
I'll run with all my might, of course with you
笑いあってもっと可愛くなる
Laughing together, I'll become even cuter
どこまででも行けちゃう気がする
I feel like I can go anywhere
今日はこのままさよならじゃないよ
Today isn't goodbye just like this
手を取ってくれたなら
If you've taken my hand
秘密も眠りにつくような夜に
On a night where even secrets fall asleep
君を連れていくよ
I will take you away
それは例えば遠く離れてたって
For example, even if we are far apart
手を繋いでいられるような
So that we can stay holding hands
奇跡のような話をしよう
Let's talk about something like a miracle
窓は開けといて
Keep the window open
今日までを思いだして
Recalling everything up until today
ひとつひとつ並べたら
If I line them up one by one
明日の雨が気になりだして
I start to worry about tomorrow's rain
どうも眠れないみたいだ
It seems I can't sleep at all
変わりたくないことや
Things I don't want to change
変わらなきゃいけないことも
And things that must change
少しは忘れたまま窓の外
Leaving them behind a bit, out the window
眺めていたんだ
I was gazing out
雨が降り出すその前に
Before the rain starts to fall
君のところまで行けるような
I feel like I can make it
気がして
to where you are
目を閉じてみたんだ
I tried closing my eyes
このまま遠くへと行こう
Let's go far away just like this
手を取ってくれるかな
Will you take my hand?
秘密も眠りにつくような夜を
A night where even secrets fall asleep
君と泳いでいくよ
I'll swim through it with you
街の明かりが消えるたびに笑って
Laughing every time the city lights go out
路地裏で立ち会おう
Let's meet in the back alley
バカみたいな話をしよう
Let's talk about something silly
窓は開けといて
Keep the window open
聞こえる
I can hear it
次は、マリン！
Next is Marine!
君たち、二日目も盛り上がっていきますよ！
Everyone, let's keep the energy up on day two!
いいわしゃーまりん！
Ready to go, Marine!
どっちが好きなのよ！
Which one do you like?!
何とかなんないかな
Can't we do something about this?
隣のあいつが邪魔だな
That guy next to me is in the way
行くないそんなこと
Don't go doing that
ダメダメだ 全力疾走絶対
No, no, no! Sprints are a must
ドバドバ違うな 何だって競争
Overflowing, no, it's a competition regardless
苦手だそういうの
I'm not good at that kind of thing
行きたくない 言い訳ばかり 地団駄の優柔不断 ダ・ダ・ダ
I don't want to go, just making excuses, stomping my feet in indecision, da-da-da
ハニ・バニ・ダリ・ダリ マジな話 どっちどっちが好きなのよ
Honey, bunny, darling, darling, seriously, which one do you like?
ダメダメダメ 余所見しないで
No, no, no, don't look away
ダメダメダメ もう逃げ出したい
No, no, no, I want to run away already
けどやるしかない
But I have to do it
正味賞味しなさい 反対方向
Enjoy me for real, in the opposite direction
WANTED!
次はぺこら！
Next is Pekora!
全力Jumping! 行くぺこだー！
Full Power Jumping! Here I go-peko!
ステップバイステップを欠かさなしで
Without missing a step-by-step
歌いながら気の向く方へ
Singing along, towards wherever I feel like
迷ってるの？ 冒険してるの？
Are you lost? Are you on an adventure?
それはみんな次第
That's up to all of you
まだまだ楽しみ足りない！
Not enough fun yet!
でもでも時間も足りない！
But even the time isn't enough!
わくわくする明日へ
To an exciting tomorrow
思い切り張り切って 前向いてさ 進もう せーの！
Give it your all, look forward, and let's go! Ready, go!
歌って本気で (ハイハイ！)
Sing with all your heart (Hi! Hi!)
遊びつくしちゃえ (ハイハイ！)
Play to your heart's content (Hi! Hi!)
やりすぎちゃうくらいで イッツ・オール・オッケー！
Even if it's a bit too much, it's all okay!
早起きよりも (ハイハイ！)
More than waking up early (Hi! Hi!)
よっしゃを！ (ハイハイ！)
Let's go! (Hi! Hi!)
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because everything will work out somehow
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
Because a pinch will become a chance
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
If we all laugh together, we're invincible
何事全力で突き抜けちゃって (ハイハイ！)
Break through everything with all your power (Hi! Hi!)
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings
ホップステップで飛び出そう
Let's jump out with a hop, step
なかなかお布団から出られない日もある
There are days when I just can't get out of bed
でも明日から そう明日から
But from tomorrow, yes, from tomorrow
本気出すんだ
I'll give it my all
気が済むまで 日が暮れるまで
Until I'm satisfied, until the sun goes down
無限大の楽しさで イッツ・オール・オッケー！
With infinite fun, it's all okay!
早起きよりも (ハイハイ！)
More than waking up early (Hi! Hi!)
よっしゃを！ (ハイハイ！)
Let's go! (Hi! Hi!)
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because everything will work out somehow
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
Because a pinch will become a chance
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
If we all laugh together, we're invincible
何事全力で突き抜けちゃって (ハイハイ！)
Break through everything with all your power (Hi! Hi!)
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings
ホップステップで飛び出そう
Let's jump out with a hop, step
最後はノエル！ あーい！ みんな、シャッフルメドレー最後まで盛り上がっていくぞー！
Finally it's Noel! A-ye! Everyone, let's keep the energy up until the end of the medley!
苦い恋の果て 残されたデッドコール
At the end of a bitter love, a left-behind dead call
出処不明のカネの山
A pile of bells from unknown origins
あいつの気配がするものは未練ばかりで
Everything with a trace of him is nothing but regrets
食えやしない
And I can't even eat it
私は生きながら化けて出る 鏡の前で早変わり
I'll haunt you while I'm still alive, quick-change in front of the mirror
パイパイ仮面でどうかしな
How about some Paipai Kamen?
今宵もひと暴れ
Another rampage tonight
踊れ踊り踊れ
Dance, dance, dance
乱れ髪 弾む胸
Disheveled hair, bouncing chest
毒迷の罠に酔いしれて
Drunken in the trap of poisonous delusions
チャヤスポット！ チャヤスポット！ チャヤスポット！ ライトミナ！
Chaya Spot! Chaya Spot! Chaya Spot! Light me up!
ほい！ や！ ほい！ や！ ほぱぱぱほい！ ホーイ！
Hoi! Ya! Hoi! Ya! Ho-pa-pa-pa-hoi! Ho-i!
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
Paipai Kamen is a multi-millionaire
ほい！ や！ ほい！ や！ ほぱぱぱほい！ ホーイ！
Hoi! Ya! Hoi! Ya! Ho-pa-pa-pa-hoi! Ho-i!
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar high
ほい！ や！ ほい！ や！ 踊れよ
Hoi! Ya! Hoi! Ya! Dance!
斬才万歳 恋シャワー
Genius, long live the love shower
せつなを生きろよ
Live for the moment
瞬間クライマックス
The climax of the moment
浮世 忘れて耽ける
Forget the fleeting world and indulge
Dancing high high high ho-ya!
ディスコティックうい
Discotheque oui
パイパイ仮面
Paipai Kamen
パイ パパイ パパッパヤ！
Pai papai pa-pappaya!
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
Paipai Kamen is a multi-millionaire
パイ パパイ パパッパヤ！
Pai papai pa-pappaya!
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar up
ホッパッパッを踊れよ
Dance the Hoppappa
三拝万拝恋シャワー
Three bows, ten thousand bows, love shower
セッパッパッを生きろよ
Live the Seppappa
瞬間クライマックス
Momentary climax
浮世 忘れてフケる ダシンハイ
Forget the floating world and run away, Dashinhai
ハイヤ ハイヤ
Haiya Haiya
ディスコ・ディップク・クイー パイパイ仮面
Disco Dippuku Kuii Paipai Kamen
じゃ、早速自己紹介からして行きますか？
Well, shall we start with the self-introductions?
して行きましょう！
Let's do it!
はい！じゃ、みんなぺこら久しぶりのあの挨拶行くから
Yes! Well, everyone, Pekora is going to do
that greeting for the first time in a while...
わかるよねみんな！あの挨拶だよ！
You all know it, right! It's that greeting!
どの挨拶だ？
Which greeting is it?
あれだ！あれしかない！
That one! It can only be that one!
行くぞー！
Here we go!
ドドンガドンドン！全人類VTuber...
Dodon-ga-don-don! All humanity VTuber...
大丈夫か？
Are you okay?
もう一回ね！もう一回目！行きます！
One more time! For real this time! Here I go!
ドドンガドンドン！全VTuber一超絶可愛いのは誰だー！
Dodon-ga-don-don! Who's the most
transcendently cute VTuber of all!
ドドンガドンドン！ドーン！
Dodon-ga-don-don! Doon!
ぺこらー！
Pekora!
やっとできました！ありがとう！
I finally did it! Thank you!
じゃ、次はフレア！
Well, next is Flare!
はい！じゃ、フレアはハイダーリンっていうので
Yes! Well, I'll say "Hi Darling"...
ハイハニーって返してください！
So please reply with "Hi Honey"!
行きますよー！
Here I go!
ハイダーリン！
Hi Darling!
ハイハニー！
Hi Honey!
ありがとう！ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
Thank you! I'm Shiranui Flare
from Hololive's 3rd generation!
そして！
And next!
はい！えー、どうしようかな今日... えー、じゃあ、
Yes! Um, what should I do today... Um, well,
こんまっするーっていうから普通にこんまっするーで！
I'll say "Konmassuru", so just say
"Konmassuru" back!
牛丼はいいのか？
What about gyuudon?
牛丼もね... 牛丼はまあ... あ、やべやべ...
Gyuudon too... well, gyuudon is... Oh, oops, oops...
あばばばばばば...
Ababababababa...
行くぞー！せーの！
Here we go! One, two!
こんまっするー！
Konmassuru!
はい！ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです！
Yes! I'm Shirogane Noel
from Hololive's 3rd generation!
そして！
And next!
君たち！本物のパイパイカメンは誰ー！
You guys! Who is the real Paipai Kamen!
マリンー！
Marine!
一番強いパイパイカメン！パイパイカメン！
The strongest Paipai Kamen! Paipai Kamen!
昨日からさ、ぺこらに船長取られるし、ノエルにパイパイカメン...
Since yesterday, Pekora's been taking my "Captain" title,
and Noel's been "Paipai Kamen"...
船長です！
I'm the Captain!
本物のパイパイカメン奪われたわけですからね！悲しい！
My "real Paipai Kamen" title was stolen! It's so sad!
ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
I'm Houshou Marine, Captain of the Houshou Pirates,
from Hololive's 3rd generation!
ついーに DAY2!
Finally, DAY 2!
DAY2！DAY2ですよ！
DAY 2! It's DAY 2!
昨日と衣装違くない？
Isn't the outfit different from yesterday?
あれ！わかりましたみんな！
Oh! Did everyone notice!
悪魔になっちゃった！
We've turned into devils!
あら！天使から悪魔っぽくなってしまったかな？
Oh! Maybe we've gone from angels
to being devil-like?
実はこれ初めて公開するんですよね！
Actually, this is the first time we're revealing this!
みんなびっくりしたかな？
I wonder if everyone was surprised?
可愛いー！
You're cute!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
でも悪魔、なんか... 結構マリンは小悪魔系で売ってるんで...
But as for devils... I usually market myself
as the "little devil" type...
かなりシナジーあるかな？
So maybe there's quite a synergy?
ぺこらも小悪魔系で売ってるからシナジー...
Pekora also markets herself as the
"little devil" type, so the synergy...
お前はアクマや！あくま！あくま！
You're just a demon! Demon! Demon!
小悪魔！
Little devil!
なんなんそのアダルトな...
What's with that adult-like...
天使と悪魔どっちが好き君たち？
Which do you guys like better, angels or devils?
あ、確かに！
Oh, true!
じゃ、ハイで言ってもらえば？ペンライトの色とかあったかな？
Then, how about having them say "Yes"?
Were there colors for the penlights?
白と赤？
White and red?
じゃ、悪魔派は赤、天使派は白！
Okay, red for the devil faction, white for the angel faction!
掲げてください！
Please hold them up!
お、でも結構いい感じに割れてる！
Oh, but it's split pretty well!
若干赤が多い？
Slightly more red?
あれ！悪魔の方が人気？
Oh! Are devils more popular?
いや、でもなんか... あ、でも半分半分かも！
No, but... oh, maybe it's half and half!
すげーやってるね！
They're really doing it!
ありがとう！えー、じゃ、今日いいね、悪魔な感じも！
Thank you! Um, well, today is great,
with the devilish feel too!
これをDAY2に取っておいたぺこね！
We saved this for DAY 2, peko!
そしてDAY1に引き続き、バンドも生演奏となっております！
And following DAY 1, we have a live band performance as well!
ありがとう！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you very much!
なんだかカッコいいですね、これね。
This is kind of cool, isn't it?
カッコいい！
It's cool!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
嬉しいですよ。
I'm so happy.
そして配信のコメントももちろん見えてますよ！
And of course, we can see the stream comments too!
見えてるよー！みんなー！
We see you! Everyone!
もう、もちろん会場のみんなももちろん当たり前よ！
And of course, everyone at the venue, that's a given!
見えてるよー！
We see you!
素敵な気合の入った推し活ファッションしてきてくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you for coming in your wonderful fan fashion!
ありがとうー！可愛いー！
Thank you! So cute!
最高最高ですよ。
It's the best, the best.
最高ですね。
It really is.
いやもう、しょっぱなね、シャッフルメドレーでしたけど。
Wow, that was a shuffle medley right from the start.
すごーいよ。
It was amazing.
ヤバかったよね。
It was crazy, wasn't it?
アゲアゲになってたよね。
It really got hyped up, didn't it?
でもですね、なんとですね、ここまでで...
But, you know, up until here...
冒頭無料チラ見せが終了となります！
The initial free sneak peek part ends here!
嘘でしょ！？ まじで！？ 嘘ですよ！
No way!? Seriously!? You're lying!
嘘ぺこでしょ！
That's a lie, peko!
そうなんですね、嘘ではないぺこです。
That's right, it's not a lie, peko.
みんな見たいと思ってくれてると思うから...
I think everyone wants to see more, so...
概要欄に配信チケットリンクあるので、今ポチポチと買ってみてください！
There's a ticket link in the description, so buy them now!
お願いしまーす！
Please!
後悔させない！
We won't let you regret it!
今日はすごい！
Today is amazing!
今日ももっともっとブチ上げ...
Today as well, even more, let's get even more hyped...
まだすごいのガンガン...
There's still more amazing stuff coming...
もうブチ上げブチ上げで準備してますから。
We're ready to get hyped up, hyped up.
Day 1とは違ったね、草の盛り上がり。
The excitement was different from Day 1, wasn't it?
そう！ 君たちも今日超ブチ上がりなんで...
Right! You guys are also super hyped today, so...
頑張って最後まで息切れしないようにブチ上がってください！
Do your best and stay hyped until the end!
最後までね、しっかり声出してね！
Give it your all and let your voices out until the end!
出してね！
Let it out!
ハッシュタグ #きゅるるん大作戦DAY2 にいっぱい呟いてください！
Please tweet using the hashtag #KyururunDaisakusenDay2!
お願いしまーす！
Please!
じゃあ、ドキドキするね。
Well, it's exciting.
そろそろ...
It's about time...
いいですか？
Are you ready?
行きますか？
Shall we go?
次の曲に行ってもいいでしょうか？
May we proceed to the next song?
いってみましょう！
Let's go!
それではですね、次の曲はなんと私からスタートさせていただきます！
Well then, the next song will start with me!
じゃあ、次の曲行きましょう！
Well then, let's go to the next song!
きゅるるんメドレー！
Kyururun Medley!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.